<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="amatherne.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="amatherne.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-07-19T03:26:53+00:00</updated><id>amatherne.github.io/</id><title type="html">AM</title><subtitle>ubuild-jekyll is a Jekyll theme desgined to work with Forestry's Blocks feature.  This theme provides a set of page-level components and a pre-configured Forestry Blocks UI  that will empower content editors to construct their own webpages.</subtitle><author><name>Forestry.io</name></author><entry><title type="html">Vetter Kids</title><link href="amatherne.github.io/posts/vetter-kids/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vetter Kids" /><published>2018-07-15T20:53:53+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-15T20:53:53+00:00</updated><id>amatherne.github.io/posts/vetter-kids</id><content type="html" xml:base="amatherne.github.io/posts/vetter-kids/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;customer-bio&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customer Bio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vetter Kids are a grunge/punk band based out of Austin, Tx. They play with passion and love interactions with their fans; whether onstage, online, or in real life. They’ve been on tours all over the Midwest and Eastcoast supporting thier 2 releases, “III” and “Logan”. Often opening for national acts like Ranier Maria, The Dillinger Escape Plan, and Reggie Watts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;goals&quot;&gt;Goals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give the band an outlet to reach their fans in a more personal way than a Facebook or Twitter Post. As well as an easier way for fans to find their upcoming shows in a centralized place the band can control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-aspects&quot;&gt;Design Aspects&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a personal test of not only myself, but of new technology, almost all design work for the Vetter Kids site was done on my iphone using the Adobe Comp CC app (Illustrator to clean up). There were many limitations of course(gradients for instance), but it was fun to be able to immediately try out a new design idea anywhere…like in line at HEB.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The band can create posts in a variety of categories: shows, featured, (1 of 4) band member, and tours. Each post can have a title, date, author, category, or header image. The categories are selected by the paths/tags that are designated in the front matter of each post. This will allow the band to designate Feature posts separately from the posts on the Tour pages, and even individual band member posts. They also have the ability to put shows in a self populating Upcoming shows with whatever information they could want.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Forestry.io</name></author><category term="Music" /><category term="Web Development" /><summary type="html">Customer Bio</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="amatherne.github.io/%7B%22background_image%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22mobile_background_image%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22image_background_color%22=%3E%22rgb(128,%2067,%2067)%22,%20%22mix_blend_mode%22=%3E%22multiply%22,%20%22background_position%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22background_size%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22mobile_background_position%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22mobile_background_size%22=%3E%22%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Austin Pedicab Company</title><link href="amatherne.github.io/posts/austin-pedicab-company/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Austin Pedicab Company" /><published>2018-07-10T04:27:02+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-10T04:27:02+00:00</updated><id>amatherne.github.io/posts/austin-pedicab-company</id><content type="html" xml:base="amatherne.github.io/posts/austin-pedicab-company/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;customer-bio&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customer Bio&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Austin Pedicab Co. was created in 2015 by a group of veteran drivers. They each have multiple years of experience in the transportainment industry and wanted to come together to make a company they could be proud to call their own. They’ve proven their mettle on the streets of Austin, New Orleans, Chicago, St Louis, and Dallas. They are adept at safely weaving the huge crowds that descend upon SXSW, Austin City Limits, Lollapolooza, Ranger/Cowboys Games, The Jazz Heritage Festival, and Mardi Gras among many others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;goals&quot;&gt;Goals &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are developing a webapp and website that will allow Users to hail a pedicab from anywhere just by inputing their number and pushing a button. It will eventually come with location services so the drivers get notified with an address to pick up at. They will also begin offering a booking service for food truck tours, margarita tours, pub crawls, bike yoga, bachelor/bachelorette parties, weddings, birthdays and for any other reason at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-aspects&quot;&gt;Design Aspects &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initial designs for this project were done as wireframes in Illustrator. For the colors schemes I wanted to capture the feel of downtown Austin at night. The reds and greens I especially wanted to give a slightly neon tinge. The header typeface is called Roadgeek and is very similar to what is used on road and street signs across the country; with all body copy being presented in Oxygen. Because the goal was to have this service available to anyone on any device or screen size, all HTML and CSS/SASS was written with a mobile first priority. To help ensure fallbacks and proper cross-browser compatibilty [Bourbon.io](&lt;a href=&quot;https://bourbon.io&quot; title=&quot;https://bourbon.io&quot;&gt;https://bourbon.io&lt;/a&gt;) was also implemented. A Basic Jekyll Blog is the basis for the CMS construct, though the only pieces of the Basic left are the liquid tags for templating all original content and CSS was removed completely. The [Twilio API](&lt;a href=&quot;https://twilio.io&quot; title=&quot;https://twilio.io&quot;&gt;https://twilio.io&lt;/a&gt;) was used to power the Cab Call feature. I had a friend who’d recently graduated from The Iron Yard help me with the php setup. The API sends one message to the customer who needs a ride and another to the company for dispatch. The dispatch is given all the info needed to contact and confirm with the customer&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Forestry.io</name></author><category term="Web Development" /><category term="Blog" /><summary type="html">Customer Bio </summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="amatherne.github.io/%7B%22background_image%22=%3E%22/uploads/2018/07/12/about-hero.png%22,%20%22mobile_background_image%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22image_background_color%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22mix_blend_mode%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22background_position%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22background_size%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22mobile_background_position%22=%3E%22%22,%20%22mobile_background_size%22=%3E%22%22%7D" /></entry></feed>